{
    "subject": "resource/Roy_Peter_Clark",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York_City",
    "human_readable": "Roy Peter Clark was born in New York City.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9342702627182007,
            "question": "Where was Roy Peter Clark born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8585402369499207,
            "question": "When was Roy Peter Clark born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5279214382171631,
            "question": "What is Roy Peter Clark known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.506231427192688,
            "question": "What is the name of Roy Peter Clark's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4419924318790436,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about Roy Peter Clark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3400825560092926,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Roy Peter Clark's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26582151651382446,
            "question": "Does Roy Peter Clark have any notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.261270135641098,
            "question": "What are some of Roy Peter Clark's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22127752006053925,
            "question": "Is Roy Peter Clark associated with any specific field or industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2074625939130783,
            "question": "Has Roy Peter Clark received any awards or recognition?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roy Peter Clark was born in New York City.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3397_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Roy Peter Clark associated with any specific field or industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3397_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Roy Peter Clark's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3397_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Roy Peter Clark have any notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3397_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3397_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all four files mention that Roy Peter Clark was born in 1948 on the Lower East Side of New York City."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Roy Peter Clark was born in New York City.\" Specifically, one of the documents states: \"Clark was born in 1948 on the Lower East Side of New York City,\" which confirms his birthplace as New York City."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}